The origin of this circulatory system that develops in these vascular blood islands
这种循环系统的起源，它在这些血管岛中发育。
which are found in the duplication of my vitelline vesicle.
它们存在于卵黄囊的分裂中。
It will have a speed that will develop later with my amniotic cavity
它将随着羊膜腔的形成而获得一个速度。
which will develop and the resorption as the integration of this entire vascular system
它的发育以及整个血管系统的吸收和整合。
inward.
向内。
We will see the appearance of a system called the primitive aortic system
我们将看到一个被称为原始主动脉系统的系统出现。
with the future heart that will develop and the system we call the valves.
伴随着未来心脏的发育以及我们称之为静脉的系统。
A synonym is the mesonephric veins.
它的一个同义词是中肾静脉。
They will already play a very important role in purification in relation to the first kidneys that will develop.
它们将对未来发育的原始肾脏起到非常重要的净化作用。
We see more and more the integration of these vessels at the level
我们看到这些血管在...水平上越来越多地整合。
of the aortic system.
...主动脉系统。
We see the importance of these vitelline veins, remember, which will form here a whole
我们看到这些卵黄静脉的重要性，请记住，它们将在这里形成一个完整的...
plexus at the beginning,
...最初的丛。
which is called the vitelline artery plexus that integrates here, whose vestige
我们称之为卵黄动脉丛，它在这里整合，其残余。
will later remain the mesenteric system that we will use.
稍后将成为我们使用的肠系膜系统。
We see here the umbilical arteries
我们在这里看到脐动脉。
which will later join here
它们稍后将在这里汇合。
and we will see here that we have
我们在这里将看到我们有
our digestive tube and we have what are called bronchial arches.
我们的消化道，以及我们称之为咽弓的结构。
You have the bronchial arch which we call pharyngeal pouch number 1, number 2, number 3, number 4
你们有被称为第1、第2、第3、第4咽囊的咽弓。
up to 6.
直到第6个。
We see, look, that there are
你们看，我们看到有
one, two, three, four and then
一、二、三、四，然后。
because in fact there is one but it appears and disappears very quickly.
因为实际上有一个，但它出现后很快就消失了。
We remove it in the literature, we describe it, we don't say 4, we don't say 5,
在文献中我们将其删除，我们描述了它，我们不说4，不说5。
but we say 6 at the beginning.
但我们最初说有6个。
What will be interesting to see is the relationship of this entire vascular system that will change
有趣的是，我们将看到整个血管系统的关系将如何变化。
and the main points to remember are that when we work at the level of the skull,
需要记住的重点是，当我们处理颅骨时。
with the brain and this vascular system,
伴随着大脑和这个血管系统。
we must realize that we have this arch of the aorta that comes from a lot of different segments.
我们必须意识到，主动脉弓是由许多不同的节段形成的。
It will be observed that the brain will be vascularized essentially by
我们将观察到大脑主要由
my carotid arteries and by my posterior vertebral arteries.
颈动脉和椎动脉供血。
Four vascular entry points, four things I should check, four
四个血管入口，四个我需要检查的方面，四个
things I will be able to work with.
我可以进行治疗的方面。
But don't forget that it's always a balance on the capillary beds, it's the exchange between
但请记住，这始终是毛细血管床上的平衡，是
your arterial system and your venous system.
动脉系统和静脉系统之间的交换。
So these are zones of energy transfer, it's a balance.
所以这些是能量传递区域，是一种平衡。
between what comes in and what goes out. You have the arterial, venous system, and then
在输入和输出之间。你有动脉系统、静脉系统，然后
the result in relation to my capillary beds will later give what is called the
相对于毛细血管床的最终结果，稍后将形成我们所说的
lymphatic system. It's the perspiration that occurs and that will create another network
淋巴系统。这是液体渗出，并将创建另一个网络
even more specific for cleaning. And so it's important that we have the zone at the same time
更具体的清洁网络。因此，重要的是我们同时拥有这个区域
to irrigate and to disengage. And there we will see that
用于灌注和引流。在这里我们将看到
there is a continuity with the
它与
vertebral plexus.
椎静脉丛有连续性。
we had already talked about yesterday. Each branchial arch will give a very specific arterial structure.
我们昨天已经讨论过。每个鳃弓将形成一个非常特定的动脉结构。
Branchial arch number 1, what is it? The vestige will be my maxillary artery.
第一鳃弓，其遗迹将是上颌动脉。
But at the same time, on the skeletal derivatives, I have all this cartilage, but
但同时，在骨骼衍生物方面，我有所有的软骨，但
that it will have
它将拥有
all the derivatives up to the level of my inner ears. For children, it's very important.
所有衍生物直到内耳水平。对于儿童来说，这非常重要。
They don't really like us touching their skull. On the other hand, they like us to
他们不太喜欢别人触碰他们的颅骨。相反，他们喜欢我们
come into their viscerocranium.
触碰他们的面颅。
It's the brain that will form the skull.
是大脑形成颅骨。
Whereas here, it's the space around that will decide the formation
而在这里，是周围空间决定了
of the digestive tube.
消化道的形成。
Remember, there were lines of force that were established,
请记住，存在着已建立的力线，
what we called in the form of dural sheaths.
我们称之为硬脑膜鞘。
And all these dural sheaths, anterior, middle, posterior,
所有这些硬脑膜鞘，前部、中部、后部，
were oriented towards my skull base.
都指向我的颅底。
And we had seen that all my bronchial arches were oriented towards this skull base,
我们还看到，所有的鳃弓都指向这个颅底，
which was this reference point, this fulcrum.
这是参考点，这个支撑点。
both vascular, neurological, visceral, etc.
血管、神经、内脏等。
What is important is to make a balance at the posterior, middle or anterior part.
重要的是在后部、中部或前部达到平衡。
I have the whole system of branchial arches number 1, maxillary artery,
我有第一咽弓的整个系统，上颌动脉，
I have the cartilage of my kelles and remember, I have all the stabilization for the tympanic canal.
我有麦克尔软骨，请记住，我有鼓室导管的全部稳定结构。
It is necessary to reconnect or allow this movement to rebalance towards its fulcrum, which is the base
必须重新连接或让这个运动重新平衡，朝向其支点，也就是基础
of the skull.
颅底。
And there, we will leave...
然后，我们将让...
the space. Branchial arch number 1, the vestige, will give us what is called the
空间。第一咽弓的残迹将形成所谓的
maxillary artery.
上颌动脉。
Then I have the second branchial arch which is what is called the hyoid system,
然后我有第二咽弓，也就是所谓的舌骨系统，
the superior
喉部
laryngeal, the inferior laryngeal, up to the thymic level. And so there I have the whole system that
上喉、下喉，直到胸腺水平。因此，我拥有所有组织起来的系统，
organizes itself on my vascular plane. It organizes itself together. If
在我的血管平面上组织起来。它们共同组织。如果
I take a skull, I will have
我拿一个颅骨，我将会有
the dural sheaths that come to be placed here, like
硬脑膜鞘会在这里放置，像
this, at my skull base, and all
这样，在我的颅底，并且所有
my branchial arches, also, it's the same way.
我的咽弓，同样地，也是以同样的方式。
This is my reference point, you see, and everything organizes around that level.
你看，这是我的参考点，一切都围绕着这个水平组织起来。
This will be my neurocranium, this will be my viscerocranium, but
这是我的神经颅，那是我的面颅，但是
in my viscerocranium,
在我的面颅中，
I find branchial arch number 1, where I will have the arch...
我会发现第一咽弓，在那里我将会有上颌弓。
maxillary. Branchial arch number 2, I will have the stapedial artery and
第二咽弓，我将会有镫骨动脉和
the tympanic artery.
鼓室动脉。
In 3, I will find myself with the common carotid. In 4, I will
在第三弓中，我将会有颈总动脉。在第四弓中，我将会有
find myself with
主动脉和锁骨下动脉。在第五弓中，没有。并且
the aorta and the subclavian arteries. And in 5, there are none. And
在第六弓中，将是肺动脉。
in 6, it will be pulmonary.
整个系统形成一个功能单位，例如与喉部
The whole system forms a functional unit with, for example, the laryngeal cartilages,
软骨，
laryngeal,
与内在肌。
with the intrinsic muscles.
avec les muscles intrinsèques.
and among others with the recurrent branch of the vagus nerve.
尤其与迷走神经返支相关。
I work with these units, I simply give fulcrums,
我与这些结构协同工作，仅仅提供支点，
I let the lines of motility develop, the meeting of the neutrals,
让动度线得以发展，中性点的会聚，
so which can carry by the meeting of the two neutrals, make the emergence,
从而通过两个中性点的相遇，促使其显现，
and the tide, the small tide or the great tide, can intervene.
潮汐，无论是小潮还是大潮，都可能介入。
Look how the face carries a vascularity.
看看面颅是如何承载着巨大的血管分布。
enormous. Your face, even your bones, even your skin, even your cartilages, it's neural crest,
巨大的。你的面部，甚至你的骨骼，你的皮肤，你的软骨，都源自神经嵴，
it's neural crest,
实际上是中外胚层。你看，我不仅会在这里放置支点，
it's mesoectoderm in fact. Not only do I have the fulcrums that will be placed here, you see,
但在此之前，我有所谓的神经嵴迁移，前脑，
see,
中脑，
but before that, I have what I call the flow of the neural crest, prosencephalon,
菱脑，然后我有菱脑1、2、3、4、5、6、7。在这个发展阶段，
mesencephalon,
这种迁移，这种蔓延。
rhombencephalon, and then I have rhombencephalon 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7. In this phase of
神经嵴覆盖我的外胚层，
development,
这是一个重要的初步信息。
this kind of flow like that, this invasion.
然后，我将拥有整个组织结构，
of the neural crest on my ectoderms,
关于我的咽弓，
which is a first important piece of information.
以及我的力线，
Then after, I will have the whole organization
总是指向同一个支点，
in relation to my bronchial arches
这是一个非常重要的支点，
and in relation to my lines of force
那就是我的颅底。
always towards the same fulcrum,
所以我们看到它对应着，
which is a very important fulcrum,
脊索的尖端。
which is my skull base.
在动脉层面，它提供运动。
So we had seen that it corresponded
在血液动力学层面，它允许，
to the tip of the notochord.
容量平衡。
At the arterial level, it gives movement.
和压力平衡，而静脉系统则更多是交换层面，
It allows, on the hemostatic level,
Elle permet, sur le plan hémostasique,
a volume balance.
un équilibre de volume.
and pressure, while the venous system is more a level of exchange,
et  de  pression,  tandis  que  le  système  de  véno,  c 'est  plus  un  niveau  d 'échange,
more a level
更深层次
osmotic, while the lymph is all about elimination, toxic elimination,
渗透性层面，而淋巴则负责所有排泄，包括毒素清除，
immunity,
免疫，
you see, everything that is CSF, that's the controller, disease of
你看，所有脑脊液，它是疾病的
control, it's the one that maintains
控制者，是它维持着
the molecular and hormonal balance specific to the body. And the return, always in
身体特有的分子和荷尔蒙平衡。而回流，始终在
the law of
的法则中，
the venous system, with the choroid plexuses,
静脉系统，伴随着脉络丛，
to produce CSF, the Pacchionian granulations to resorb it
用于制造脑脊液，以及用于吸收脑脊液的蛛网膜颗粒，
and the lymph, I remind you, which returns to the system
我提醒你们，淋巴回流到系统中，
with the great plan here of balance which are my capillary beds
伴随着这里宏大的平衡计划，那就是我的毛细血管床，
which I remind you, is the meeting place between the arterial and venous system.
我提醒你们，它是动脉系统和静脉系统之间的交汇点。
Each time at the level of the capillary beds, a transformation of energy,
每次在毛细血管床层面，都会发生能量转化，
a rebalancing of the rhythmic zones and a system on the vasoregulation of the planes.
节律区的再平衡，以及平面血管调节系统。
These are guardians of homeostatic balance on a fluidic level.
这些是流体层面上稳态平衡的守护者。
It also corresponds to copula zones, specific rhythmic zones.
它也对应着连接区，即特定的节律区。
This is a rhythmic zone, this is a rhythmic zone, this is a rhythmic zone.
这是一个节律区，那是一个节律区，这又是一个节律区。